{
    "id": "eee1baddcec14dc387229505570ed878",
    "title": "Adjectives Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The elephant is a large animal. The rabbit is a ................................. animal.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "small",
                "little"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It is cold in winter. It is ....................................... in summer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hot",
                "heated"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Yesterday it was cloudy. Today is a ................................. day.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sun",
                "sunny"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "These shirts are wet. Haven’t you got a ....................................... one?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "dry",
                "dried"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We won’t reach there in time if we go by a slow train. We must catch a .................................... train.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "faster",
                "fast"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "My shoes are old. I want to buy a .................................. pair.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "new",
                "fresh"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Some colors are bright. Others are ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "black",
                "pale",
                "dark"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "It is warm outside. It is ....................................... inside.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "cool",
                "cooled"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "This bread is stale. We must buy a ................................ loaf.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "new",
                "fresh"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This knife is blunt. I need a .................................. one.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "keen",
                "sharp"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}